# Gabriel Jonas Antonius Hauss



•

+49 157 34 761 785

6211ER Maastricht

•

gabriel.hauss@gmail.com 🖾

Instagram: hello.hauss

**(A)** 

## Personal Profile

Having worked in highly communication-intense businesses, I consider myself an extroverted, outgoing person who is very benefitial for the spirit of a team. As a waiter, I keep the team spirit up and help others out where I can during stressful shifts. "There is never nothing to do in gastronomy" is what my old boss at Hans im Glück used to say and I internalised that as my work ethic.

## **Experience**

May 2019 - December 2019

Waiter • Hans im Glück Burgergrill, Essen, Germany

December 2018 - May 2019

Outbound Telesales Rep • FCS Europe, Essen, Germany

June 2018 - September 2018

Waiter, Barkeeper • Kimberley Grand Hotel, Kununurra, Australia

December 2017 - April 2018

Sales Team Leader • HelloFresh Australia, Melbourne, Australia

### **Education**

Maastricht University, Maastricht, Limburg

 Maastricht Science Programme (MSP) with focus on Physics

Grashof Gymnasium, Essen, Nordrhein-Westphalen

- GPA: 1,2
- Focus subjects: Maths and Physics

### Personal interests

Videography, photography, gymming